{
    "subject": "resource/Joaquim_Manuel_de_Macedo",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Itabora\u00ed",
    "human_readable": "Joaquim Manuel de Macedo was born in Itabora\u00ed.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9409669041633606,
            "question": "Where was Joaquim Manuel de Macedo born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7231123447418213,
            "question": "What is Joaquim Manuel de Macedo known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6785800457000732,
            "question": "What was Joaquim Manuel de Macedo's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6224237084388733,
            "question": "Was Joaquim Manuel de Macedo a writer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6007859110832214,
            "question": "Which city is associated with Joaquim Manuel de Macedo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5976652503013611,
            "question": "Who were some of Joaquim Manuel de Macedo's contemporaries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5309402346611023,
            "question": "How is Joaquim Manuel de Macedo remembered in Brazilian history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4753439724445343,
            "question": "In what year did Joaquim Manuel de Macedo die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3334135115146637,
            "question": "What political roles did Joaquim Manuel de Macedo hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31197646260261536,
            "question": "What were the major historical events during Joaquim Manuel de Macedo's lifetime?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Joaquim Manuel de Macedo was born in Itabora\u00ed.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1978_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What political roles did Joaquim Manuel de Macedo hold?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1978_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Joaquim Manuel de Macedo die?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1978_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is Joaquim Manuel de Macedo remembered in Brazilian history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1978_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1978_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1978_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1978_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1978_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1978_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1978_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1978_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1978_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1978_96.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1978_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about Joaquim Manuel de Macedo's birth and it does not specifically mention that he was born in Itabora\u00ed. In fact, the document with file_path \"/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1978/re-ranker-msmarco/7.txt\" mentions that Joaquim Manuel de Macedo (Born in Itabora\u00ed...), but this seems to be a statement about his birth location, rather than an attribution of the text itself. Therefore, it cannot be considered as evidence that the triple is correct."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis answer is based on the information provided in the documents, which state that \"Joaquim Manuel de Macedo was born in the city of Itabora\u00ed, in 1820,\" confirming that Joaquim Manuel de Macedo was indeed born in Itabora\u00ed."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "All sources mention Joaquim Manuel de Macedo was born in the city of Itabora\u00ed, but then later mention he started to practice medicine and published his romance A Moreninha in Rio, without mentioning that it's a different place from where he was born.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}